// creating an array of objects and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    answer: "Sadio Mane",
    options: ["Erling Haaland", "Sadio Mane", "Jamie Vardy", "Sergio Aguero"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who Is The Greatest Footballer Ever?",
    answer: "Lionel Messi",
    options: ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Pele", "Maradona", "Lionel Messi"],
  },

  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "The fastest goal scored in Premier League history came in 7.69 seconds. Who scored it?",
    answer: "Shane Long",
    options: ["Shane Long", "Harry Maguire", "Harry Kane", "Bowen"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which country has won the most World Cups?",
    answer: "Brazil",
    options: ["Uruguay", "Spain", "Brazil", "France"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Which country has appeared in three World Cup finals, but never won the competition?",
    answer: "Netherlands",
    options: ["Netherlands", "Belgium", "South Korea", "Portugal"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Ronaldo exclaims which word when celebrating a goal?",
    answer: "i'm Finished",
    options: ["Suiiiii", "Weweee", "Let's go", "i'm Finished"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Messi has won a record number of Ballon d'Or awards - how many? ",
    answer: "7",
    options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "I was originally a striker before becoming a defender. I played 11 seasons for the same club before managing them. I've won two Bundesliga titles and a Champions League. Who am i?",
    answer: "Jurgen Klopp",
    options: [
      "Josep Guardiola",
      "Jurgen Klopp",
      "Carlo Ancelotti",
      "Xavi Hernandez",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Is Cristiano Ronaldo Finished?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: ["Yes", "Yes", "Yes", "Yes"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "In video game FIFA 21, team Piemonte Calcio represents which real-life club?",
    answer: "Juventus",
    options: ["Everton", "Udinese Calcio", "Juventus", "Young Boys"],
  },
];
